你在笑什么
What's so funny?
没有  这是演技练习  我在练假笑
Nothing. It's an acting exercise. I'm practicing my fake laugh.
你在笑什么
What? What's so funny?
不行  店里不准抽烟
No, no. There's none of that in here.
别这样  兄弟  至少让我抽完这一根
Come on, man. At least let me finish this last one.
好  但你得分我一口
OK, but only if you give me a drag.
好的
Okay.
黑暗之母  我又吮吸到你冒烟的乳头了
Oh, dark mother, once again I suckle at your smoky teat.
不用了  整根都给你吧
No, no. Why don't you hold on to that one.
这是史上最不好玩的游戏
Okay, that's like the least fun game ever.
我受够了你吸烟  我带了一样东西
I'm really sick of your smoking, so I brought something...
可以帮助你戒烟
that is going to help you quit.
这个戒烟贴布不好用
That patch is no good.
这是催眠录音带
Come on, it's a hypnosis tape.
我一个女同事听了两星期
This woman at work used it for two weeks straight
就再也没抽过烟
and she hasn't smoked since.
你有什么意见
What's your problem?
没什么  只不过催眠是骗人的
Nothing. It's just that hypnosis is beyond crap.
罗斯  我在亚特兰大看过你被催眠
Ross, I watched you get hypnotized in Atlantic City.
那家伙没把我催眠  好吗
That guy did not hypnotize me, okay?
是啊  你总是脱裤子数到三
All right. Because you always pull your pants down and count to three
然后用屁股玩赛车游戏
and play "Wipe Out" on your butt cheeks.
别用催眠了
All right, forget hypnosis.
想戒烟
The way to quit smoking
就得去石南地上裸舞
is you have to dance naked in a field of heather...
然后用六个年轻壮丁的汗水沐浴
and then bathe in the sweat of six healthy, young men.
我爸管这叫"周四夜狂欢"
Or what my father calls "Thursday night."
-给你  -多谢
- Here you go. - Thanks.
不好意思  我没要加肉桂
Oh, y'know what, I didn't want cinnamon on this.
对不起
Sorry.
天哪  弗兰克
Oh, my God! Frank!
你好吗
How are you?
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我本想先打电话  但是号码弄丢了
I would've called, but I lost your phone number.
我妈把我锁在门外  我没办法进去找
And then my mom locked me out of the house, so I couldn't find it.
我找了一部公共电话
And then I tried to find a pay phone,
话筒却被剪断了
and the receiver was cut off.
怎么了
What happened?
有人破坏公物
Vandalism.
你和你妈怎么了
But also, what happened between you and your mom?
我们吵了一架  她说我不够成熟不能结婚
We got in a fight. She said that I was too immature to get married.
-你要结婚了  -是啊
- You're getting married? - Yeah.
我的弟弟要结婚了
My little brother's getting married!
我就知道你会替我高兴
I knew you'd be so cool about this.
你想见她吗
All right, do you wanna meet her?
你说呢
Do l?
你想吗
Do you?
当然想
Yeah, I do.
太好了  她正在停卡车
Cool, all right. She's just parking the truck.
我去带我的未婚妻来
I gonna go get my fiancee, man!
我就知道
You know I'd have bet good money
我们之中  他会最早结婚
that he'd be the first one of us to get married.
这不是很棒吗
Isn't it fantastic?
是啊  但菲比
Yeah, but Pheebs,
你不觉得他结婚稍嫌年轻吗
don't you think he's a little young to get married?
他已经18岁了
Well, he's 18.
没错  他在告别单身派对上喝酒还算违法
Exactly, it'll be illegal for him to drink at his own bachelor party.
也不能找妓女
Yeah, or to get a hooker.
找妓女什么时候都违法
Always illegal, Joe.
这是我的未婚妻
This is my fiancee...
奈特老师
Mrs. Knight.
那是我姐姐
That's my sister.
说来好笑
You know, it's funny.
弗兰克经常提到你
Frank told me so much about you,
你却跟我想像的完全不一样
but you're not how I pictured you at all.
是啊  我很令人意外
Yeah, I'm a big surprise.
坐吧
Here, grab a seat.
你们是怎么认识的
So how did you guys meet?
我去上奈特老师的...
I was in Mrs. Knight's....
我是说爱丽丝  抱歉  我老是叫错
I mean, Alice. Sorry. I always do that.
我去上她的家政课
I was in her home-ec class.
他是我最好的学生
He was my best student.
她是我最好的老师
She was my best teacher.
真是让学生不跷课的好方法
If that doesn't keep kids in school, what will?
这么说你们要结婚了
And so now you guys are gonna be married?
是啊  我们本来只考虑同居  但是...
Yeah. We talked about just living together but...
我们想马上生小孩
we want have kids right away.
天哪
Oh, my God!
太好了
Great!
小孩  弗兰克  你真的准备好了吗
Kids. Frank, are you sure you're ready for that?
能有多难
How hard can it be?
生宝宝  谁不想要小宝宝  对吧
You know, I mean, babies. Who doesn't want babies? Right?
而且我一直没有爸爸陪伴
And besides, I never had a dad around.
以后就有了
And now I always will,
因为我就是爸爸
because you know it'll be me.
其实
You know I mean really,
我们知道我们的岁数差很多
we do realize that there's an age difference between us.
那就好  因为你看起来好像不知道
Good. Okay. Because you were acting like you didn't.
但是在爱情里  年龄不是问题
No, but when it comes to love, what does age matter?
你正在进入梦乡
You are falling fast asleep.
越睡越沉  越睡越沉
Deeper, deeper, deeper.
你已经完全睡着了
You are now completely asleep.
你不需要抽烟
You don't need to smoke.
香烟不能控制你
Cigarettes don't control you.
你是坚强  有自信的女性
You are a strong, confident woman...
你不需要抽烟
who does not need to smoke.
坚强  有自信的女性
A strong, confident woman.
你知道吗
You know what?
我刚发现去年
I just realized in the last year
我只和理查德  胡利欧交往过
I've only gone out with two guys. Richard and Julio.
你得帮我牵线
You gotta help me out here, you gotta set me up.
让我重回情场
You gotta get me back in the game.
应该没问题
That shouldn't be a problem.
我在时装界工作  身边全是适龄异性恋男人
I work in fashion, and all I meet are eligible straight men.
你还要什么
Can I get you something else?
一块芝士蛋糕和一次约会  如果有的话
How about a slice of cheesecake and a date, if you're giving them out.
我们不是谈过了吗
Haven't you and I covered that topic?
你刚才对她说
Come on, you just said to her...
你想跟我约会
You only wanna go out with me...
是因为我是金发  波霸  还端吃的给你
because of my blond wig, the big boobs, and in fact I serve you food.
那样的话  我找我姑姑就行了
Well if that were true, I'd be dating my Aunt Ruth.
我们一起出去两次  都蛮惨的
And the two times we went out, it was plain awkward.
你也觉得她应该和我约会吧
Come on, you think she should go out with me, don't you?
那个  我是说
Well, I mean...
你真的想跟她约会吗
You sure you wanna go out with her?
早上会惨不忍睹哦  知道我意思吧
That ain't a pretty picture in the morning. You know what I mean?
假发乱成一团  假胸扔在床头柜上
That wig all in disarray, and boobs flung over the nightstand.
你考虑一下
I mean, really, think about it.
我会的
Oh, I will.
我知道这是弗兰克的人生
No, I know. I know that this is Frank's life, you know.
我不想妄下断论  但这太变态了
I don't wanna be judgmental, but it's sick.
而且大错特错
It's sick and wrong!
菲比  怎么了  因为年龄吗
Pheebs. What, is it the age thing?
我本来不在乎年龄
No, no, I'm fine with the age thing...
直到她把舌头伸进我弟的喉咙
until it sticks its tongue down my little brother's throat.
菲比  他看起来很爽
Pheebs, he seems to enjoy it.
等他忙着帮
I mean you think he's gonna enjoy it
一堆宝宝换尿布
when he's up to his elbows in diapers...
你觉得他还会爽吗
of all the babies they have to have right away?
这样对弗兰克不公平  也对宝宝不公平
This is not fair to Frank, and it's not fair to the babies.
你知道吗  这也不是好的家政
You know what? It's not good home economics.
你跟他说过你的感受吗
Have you told him how you feel?
有  但没有说出声音
Yes. Not out loud.
菲比  如果你不说
Pheebs, if you don't tell him,
他就要结婚了  你会恨你自己的
soon he's gonna be married, then you're gonna hate yourself.
我要是说了  他会恨我
Yeah, but if I do tell him, then he's gonna hate myself.
你看看他和他妈妈  我不能说
Look at him and his mom. I can't.
但是你们可以  你们去劝阻他
But you guys can. Please you guys talk him out of it.
不行
No no...
拜托啦
Come on, you guys.
你们没有损失  我却会失去一切
You have nothing to lose. I have everything to lose.
你们要我失去一切吗  失去一切
Do you want me to lose everything? Everything?
不想
No.
好  我去找弗兰克
Okay, I'm gonna go get Frank.
刚才走在街上  我对你说
So we're walking down the street, and I turn to you and say:
"去脱衣酒吧坐坐"  记得吗
"Hey let's go hang out at Totally Nude Nudes." Remember?
然后你对我说
And then you turned to me you say,
"不  去你家就好了"
"Nay, let's just hang out at your place."
好明智啊  猪头
Well, that was a nice move, dumb ass.
你绝对该跟他约会
I think you should definitely go out with this guy.
他对我一点吸引力也没有
He doesn't do anything for me.
莫妮卡  上周六晚的《德州巡警》什么剧情
Monica, last Saturday night, what happened on Walker, Texas Ranger?
沃克在找一车子的小孩
Walker was looking for this big busload of kids.
我懂你的意思了
All right, I get your point.
我一年前就忘了它的密码
I forgot the combination to this about a year ago.
我只是带着装样子
I just carry it around.
你们有护唇膏吗
You got any Chap Stick?
录音带听得怎样
How are those tapes working out for you?
很有效  我今天还没抽烟
You know what? Pretty good. Good! I haven't smoked yet today.
我感觉清爽又有自信  好漂亮的上衣
I feel great and confident. That is a stunning blouse.
谢谢
Thank you.
-拿去  -谢了
- Here you go. - Thanks.
莫妮卡  给彼特一个机会
Okay, Mon, let's give Pete a chance.
他既风趣  人看起来也很好
He was funny. He seems really nice.
而且支票的事好可爱
That check thing was adorable.
什么支票
What check thing?
餐厅有个喜欢我的顾客开玩笑
As a joke, this customer at work who has a crush on me,
给我两万元的小费
gave me a $20, 000 tip.
他的电话在支票上  他要我打给他
His number's on the check. He just did it so I'd call.
彼特·贝克  彼特
Pete Becker. Pete...
是他吗
Is this him?
那是比尔·克林顿
That's Bill Clinton.
他抱着谁
Who's he hugging?
天哪  是彼特  总统为什么抱着彼特
Oh, my God. That's Pete. Why is Bill hugging Pete?
他发明了摩斯865
This guy invented Moss 865.
全世界的公司都在用这个程序
Every office in the world uses that program.
-我们也在用  -这就对了
- We use it! - There you go!
天哪  莫妮卡要跟百万富翁约会了
Oh my God. Monica's gonna go out with a millionaire.
我才不跟他约会呢
I'm not gonna go out with him.
天哪  这居然是真的两万元支票
Oh,  my God. I can't believe this is a real $20, 000 check.
好激动
This is so exciting.
或是令人火大
Or incredibly offensive.
对  也有
Yeah, sure. That too.
怎样
What?
我们的意思是  不要操之过急
All we're saying is, don't rush into anything.
你想想  你18岁  她44岁
Come on, think about it. You're 18. Okay, she's 44.
等你36岁  她就88岁了
When you're 36, she's gonna be 88.
你以为我不知道吗
You don't think I know that?
重点是
The point is...
你还可以跟很多女人上床
there's a lot of women out there you haven't even had sex with yet.
他说得对  这是你的天下
He's right. He's right. This is your time. You know?
你年轻  你古怪  女生最喜欢了
You're young. You're weird. Chicks dig that.
跟一个你很喜欢的人做
Okay, isn't sex better when it's with one person
感觉不是更棒吗
that you really really care about?
在诗里吧
Yeah, in a poem, maybe.
不  他说得对  我跟瑞秋就是那样
No, the man's right. That's what I had with Rachel.
现在没有了吗
You don't have it anymore?
没了  我跟别人上了床
No. I slept with someone else.
等等  那样对事情有帮助吗
Okay so wait. All right. So how did that make things better?
没有
It didn't.
你跟瑞秋的感觉  就是我和爱丽丝的感觉
What you used to have with Rachel is what I got with Alice.
那是什么感觉
Now, what is that like?
很棒的感觉
It's so cool, man.
因为跟她在一起
It's because being with her is
比不跟她在一起快乐多了
so much better than not being with her.
我为什么找不到
Why can't I find that?
别问我  我拥有过  却搞砸了
Don't ask me. I had it and I blew it.
我想要
Well, I want it!
你一定可以拥有
You can have it.
也许我不行  也许我有毛病
I don't know. Maybe I can't. Maybe there's something wrong with me.
你会找到的  我见过  也拥有了
No, it's out there, man. I've seen it! I got it!
-那你就要好好把握  -好
- Then, you hold on to it! - All right, man!
死小子  恭喜你
All right! Congratulations, you lucky bastard!
你是弗兰克的伴郎
You're Frank's best man?
我没办法  他们的爱好纯洁
I couldn't help it. Their love is so pure.
那你呢
What about you, huh?
我帮他拿戒指
I'm the ring bearer.
爱丽丝  多谢  你来了就好
Alice, hi, thanks. I'm so glad you could come.
我有一个家政惨案
Because I've got a real home-ec emergency.
天哪  谁死了
Oh, my God. Who died on this?
芥末酱倒了
It's a real "mustard-tastrophe."
你有办法吗
Can you help me?
当然有  先用苏打水加盐清洗
Absolutely. Okay first, we'll start with a little club soda and salt.
要是洗不掉  就可以试着
Then if that doesn't work, then we can go back to...
算了  已经毁了
You know what? Forget it. It's ruined.
别这么说
No, no, never say that.
要是洗不掉  就剪掉脏污部分
If you can't get it out, then you can cut around the stain...
缝一点蕾丝  就是一条漂亮的盖毯
add a little lace, you make a stylish throw.
又或者  你可以不要嫁给我弟弟弗兰克
Or instead, maybe you could just not marry my brother, Frank?
很好
Okay, that's great.
能再小些吗  小到可以放在针尖上
But can we make it smaller? Can we make it fit on the head of a pin?
我喜欢生产这种小东西
I love when we make things fit on the head of a pin.
-明白  -好的
- Got it. - Okay.
莫妮卡·盖勒小姐来访
You have Miss Monica Geller here.
好的  让她进来
Absolutely. Yeah, send her in.
这算什么意思
What the hell is this?
等一下  明天早上再谈
Hang on for a sec. I'll talk to you in the morning?
好的
You got it.
对不起  什么
I'm sorry. What?
说真的  这是什么意思
Seriously. What's this supposed to mean?
我一直不会算小费
Well, you know, I never know how much to tip.
把税乘以二  不是把罗马尼亚的税收乘以二
You suppose to double the tax. Not double the tax of Romania.
什么意思  你要收买我吗
What's the deal? Are you trying to buying me?
你都这样约女孩子吗
Is this the way you get girls to go out with you?
我还在
I'm still here.
你误会了  要是我没给这笔小费
You're taking this all wrong. If I didn't leave you that tip...
你就不会来  我们不会争吵
you wouldn't have come down here, we wouldn't have this argument...
-也不会有这种紧张的气氛  -什么
- and there wouldn't be this heat between us. - What?
你得承认
Come on, you gotta admit
我们的关系有进展了
that our relationship is hitting a new level now.
以前你是厨师  我是顾客
'Cause you used to be like the chef and I was the customer.
现在我们是两个争吵的人
But now we're like this couple that fights.
你是个疯子
Okay, you're a loon.
别管这张支票了  我喜欢你
Look, forget the check, okay? I like you.
我觉得你很棒
I think you're great.
怎么样  你什么感觉
Come on, what do you say?
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么
Why not?
我不想鼓励这种行为
I don't wanna encourage this kind of behavior.
我只求一顿饭  好吗
One meal. That's all I'm asking for. Please?
我们出去吃饭
We go out, we eat.
要是玩得不开心  我给你一万  我们扯平
If you don't have a good time, I'll give you 10 grand, we're even.
不  把信放下  是我
Wait, no. Just put the mail down. It's me.
对不起  你怎么不开灯
Sorry. Why were you just like all in the dark?
你的衣服好香  我就窝在里面
Your laundry smelled so good that I thought I'd curl up in it.
-没关系吧  -没关系
- Is that all right? - Yeah, sure.
今天过得怎样
So how was your day?
可能是我有生以来最惨的一天
It's just probably the worst one since I've been alive.
怎么了
What? What happened?
爱丽丝改变心意了
Alice.... She called it off.
不是吧
Oh, no.
她有说原因吗
Did she say why?
没有  她只说我太年轻
No not really. Just that I was too young.
我怎么突然变年轻了
You know but I don't see how I could suddenly be too young...
我可比我们刚交往时老成不少
because I'm older than I was when we first got together.
是的是的  我知道
Yeah, yeah, I know.
不知道  但是你知道吗
I don't know. But you know what?
或许这样也好
Maybe it's just all for the best.
是啊  如果"好"就是我好痛苦的话
Well, yeah, if the best is like unbelievable pain.
亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
我好不容易感到快乐
You know, I was just finally happy.
这是生平第一次
You know, for the first time in my life...
先是爸爸离开我
after my dad left me...
然后偷鸟被逮捕
and then and then getting arrested for stealing those birds...
然后又肺穿孔
and then the whole punctured-lung thing.
天气一冷  我还是很难深呼吸
It's still really hard to take deep breaths in cold weather...
但是有了爱丽丝  这些都不见了
but with Alice, all that stuff kind of went away.
现在我失去了  却不知道原因
And now and now it's gone, and I don't know why.
我可以告诉你原因  是我害的
Well, I can tell you why. It's because of me.
不过我是爱你才这么做的  好吗
But you know what? I only did it because I love you, okay?
什么
What?
我跟爱丽丝聊了一下
I kind of had a little chat with Alice...
让她明白你们为何不能在一起
and I sort of made her see why you two shouldn't be together.
你总有一天也会明白的  真的
And you're gonna see it too, one day. You really, really will.
等一下  是你造成的
Wait a minute. This is because of you?
-好了  -等等
- Okay. - Wait, no.
我妈反对我们在一起
My mother didn't want us to be together...
但是她顶多把我绑在门廊上
but the worst thing she every did was tie me to the porch.
但是...
Okay, but...
我觉得你能了解  所以才来找你
You know what? I came to you because I thought you'd understand.
怎么会
No!
知道吗
You know?
我很想立刻摔门走人
I would storm out of here right now...
但是我没钱  没地方去
if I had some money or a place to go.
天哪  百万富翁来了
Oh, my God! The millionaire's here!
天哪
Oh, my God!
各位  别这样  我只是要跟他吃顿饭
Guys, please, I'm just gonna have dinner with him, okay?
好吧记住了  他请你吃饭
Okay, just because he buys you dinner
并不代表你欠他什么
does not mean you owe him anything.
我知道
I know.
那记得点龙虾
Okay, then get the lobster.
你口袋里有多少现金
How much cash you got in your pocket now?
所以我就不请你进来喝一杯了
And that's why I'm not inviting you in for a drink.
-拜  -进来坐一下嘛
- Bye. - Why not? Hey, come in for drink.
-你想去哪里  -你喜欢吃披萨吗
- Where do you wanna go? - You like pizza?
-听起来不错  -有一家馆子不错
- That sounds great. - I know a great little place.
我不能让你付比萨钱
You're not paying for the pizza.
我付吧  这样才公平  你出了机票钱
Come on, it's only fair. You paid for the flight.
这些里拉够吗
Is that enough lira?
再丢个一千
I'd throw another 1000 on that.
-这些是多少  -大约六毛美金
- How much is that? - That's about 60 cents.
每晚都这样
Every night!
你不需要抽烟
You don't need to smoke.
香烟不能控制你
Cigarettes don't control you.
你是坚强  有自信的女性
You are a strong, confident woman...
你不需要抽烟
who does not need to smoke.
坚强  有自信的女性
A strong, confident woman...
不需要抽烟
who does not need to smoke.
弗兰克
Hey, Frank.
我知道你觉得我做了大坏事
Look, okay, I know that you think I did this like totally evil thing.
但是我没有
But I so didn't.
有一个人可以解释得比我清楚
There's someone's here who I think can explain this better than I can.
嗨  弗兰克
Hi, Frank.
嗨  奈特老师
Hi, Mrs. Knight.
弗兰克  菲比说得对
Phoebe's right, Frank.
这话不中听
I know it's hard to hear,
但我们不该结婚
but it would've been wrong to go through with it.
我太自私了
I was being selfish.
尽管我们现在追求相同的东西
Even though we want the same things right now...
未来却不见得如此
in the future, we may not.
-对不对  -对  但不止如此
- Is that what it is? - Yes, but not just that.
不止如此
Right, not just that.
虽然我们现在非常相爱
Even though we love each other as much as we do...
然而
nonetheless....
Nonetheless.
你还太年轻
You're too young to...
不知道你究竟要什么
to really know what you want.
没错  就是这样
That's right, exactly.
你们在吻别  很好
All right, that's a goodbye kiss. That's good.
再见
Bye-bye.
重要的是  你了解了我的意思
The important thing is, is that you see what I'm saying.
知道吧  知道吧
You know, just you know.
这么做明显是错的
This is clearly wrong.
好吧  我决定袖手旁观了
Okay, I've decided I'm gonna let this happen.
能让我拿下皮包吗
Can I just get my purse?
好吧  算了
Okay, all right, good.
香烟不能控制你
Cigarettes don't control you.
你是坚强  有自信的女性
You are a strong, confident woman...
你不需要抽烟
who does not need to smoke.
乔伊是你最要好的朋友
Joey's your best friend.
你要每天为他做芝士三明治
You wanna make him a cheese sandwich every day.
你还要送他价值几百块的裤子
And you also wanna buy him hundreds of dollars worth of pants.